Guide to the Chloe Faith Dzubilo Papers MSS.397
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE Series III: Writing, 1988-2010
  - Envelope - Annotated, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Kodak Box - Annotated, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - [Untitled Writing], undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Who Killed Brandon Teena The Second Time?? Posters - Annotated, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- OVERSIZE Series V: Press & Ephemera, 1984-2011
  - Press, 1997-2004 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Transisters Poster, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)